Contact

cseacrist21@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/charles-seacrist-0939b413a (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS)

Basic Life Support (BLS)

Telemetry

Certifications

Critical Care Registered Nurse

Charles Seacrist

Critical Care Registered Nurse at MetroHealth RN, BSN, CCRN Cleveland/Akron, Ohio Area

Summary

Experienced Critical Care Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Critical Care, Telemetry, Basic Life Support (BLS), Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), and Life Support. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor of Science (B.S.) focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from Kent State University.

Experience

The MetroHealth System (Cleveland, OH)
Critical Care Registered Nurse
July 2017 - Present (3 years 1 month)
Cleveland/Akron, Ohio Area

Surgical Intensive Care

Marymount Hospital - Cleveland Clinic Critical Care RN September 2016 - July 2017 (11 months) Garfield Heights, OH

Education

Kent State University

Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Nursing Science · (2014 - 2016)

Kent State University

Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Integrated Health Studies/Health Science · (2011 - 2014)

The University of Akron

Masters of Science in Nursing, Nursing Science (2019)